chineseye.com 2010-01-13

# Privacy Policy - CHINESEye.com

**Privacy Policy**  
Greetings! This page contains privacy policy that rules how your information is collected and used in this website.  
This privacy policy is a part of our _Terms of Use_ and should be read carefully, as it specifies which rights you have and how you can exercise your rights. Any use of the website implies the entire acceptance of this privacy policy.  
**What we collect**  
We collect public information uploaded by you. This information comprises personal data in your profile, pictures, blogs, links, videos, events, lists, and information in your messages, ratings, including any kind of contributions to other users.  
We also collect private information uploaded by you. This information comprises your account settings, administrative data, and blacklist.  
Other information, for example, your browsing history in our website, logs, searches, and technical information regarding your computer and internet browser (including your Internet Protocol address, version and manufacturer of your browser and operating system), are also collected.  
**Why we collect**  
The data we collect are utilized to:  

  * 1.Publish the information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy          settings
  * 2.Allow you to correctly use the website in accordance with your settings
  * 3.Perform general customer administration, for example, to process payments, send usernames and     passwords, and respond to questions.
  * 4.Send you communications about the website, as well as our other products and services, under the     conditions specified by you.
  * 5.Investigate fraud and infringements of our _Rules of Conduct_
  * 6.Generate anonymous statistics of users of the website, to improve the website, or convey statistical     information to third parties  

**Third parties data sharing**  
Third parties can access all information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy settings. Your email address is NEVER shared by us with any third party (except if you voluntarily post it on your instant messenger tab and made available public). For the purpose of targeted advertisements, we share your browser type, IP address, current and previous URL you are visiting (and search query), age, gender, and geographical location with our advertisement provider. This information may subsequently be used by other websites for the display and management of targeted advertisements. We never share any of your personal data with any third party, unless you give your explicit permission. Despite all our protection to your personal data, however, we will have to provide access to it in case of illegal use, or when we receive orders from legal authorities.   
**Cookies**  
As most websites do, Chineseye uses cookies to identify you as a user of the website, to remember your preferred language and to facilitate navigation on the website. However, you can disable cookies in your internet browser although this will result on some parts of the website no longer functioning correctly.
